const aboutTexts = [
  {
    "question": "What is KRO?",
    "answer": "This platform serves as a Mint Interface for the First Inscription Token, KRO, on the Kroma Blockchain, providing a user-friendly gateway for engaging with this innovative digital asset."
  },
  {
    "question": "What are Inscriptions?",
    "answer": "Inscriptions are a novel form of on-chain digital artifacts, storing information directly on the blockchain through call data. These inscriptions can include tokens, NFTs, and more, and can be traded, collected, or stored by users."
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this the first Inscription Token?",
    "answer": "We are 99% confident that KRO is the first inscription token on Kroma, based on extensive data collection. However, due to inherent uncertainties, there's a slight margin of error."
  },
  {
    "question": "Fairness and Token Distribution",
    "answer": "Initially, only about 20,000 tokens were mined for testing and development, aiming for broad accessibility and enjoyment of this new standard."
  },
  {
    "question": "Value of the Token",
    "answer": "While we see intrinsic value in KRO, its worth is subjective and can fluctuate. Minting is free, but gas fees, which are non-refundable, apply."
  },
  {
    "question": "Understanding the Inscription Trend",
    "answer": "The surge in inscriptions on EVMs is driven by their efficiency in transaction costs, allowing for functionalities similar to smart contracts but at a lower cost."
  },
  {
    "question": "The Venmo Field in Transactions",
    "answer": "EVMs use a 'Venmo notes' field in transactions for embedding information, crucial for smart contracts and utilized by inscriptions for creating versatile NFTs and tokens."
  },
  {
    "question": "First Inscription",
    "answer": "The first recorded inscription was made in 2016 by Tom Lehman, marking a significant milestone in blockchain technology."
  },
  {
    "question": "Impact and Future Outlook",
    "answer": "Inscriptions have led to a surge in transactions, affecting gas prices and network congestion. They offer simplicity and affordability, but also pose risks of potential scams."
  },
  {
    "question": "Disclaimer",
    "answer": "This information is for general understanding and does not constitute financial advice. Conduct due diligence and be aware of risks in blockchain transactions."
  }
];

export default aboutTexts;
